<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fitness Application</string>
    <string-array name="TrainingName">
        <item>Push up</item>
        <item>Reverse</item>
        <item>Butt Kicks</item>
        <item>Knee</item>
        <item>strengthen</item>
        <item>cinch</item>
        <item>Stutter steps</item>
        <item>Rid Of Saddlebags</item>
        <item>Cross crunches</item>
        <item>Back extensions</item>
        <item>Shrimp squat</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="time">
        <item> *16 Times</item>
        <item> 30 Seconds</item>
        <item> 30 Seconds</item>
        <item> *16 Times </item>
        <item> *16 Times</item>
        <item> *16 Times</item>
        <item> 30 Seconds</item>
        <item> 30 Seconds</item>
        <item> *16 Times</item>
        <item> *16 Times</item>
        <item> 30 Seconds</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Description">
        <item>Push up exercise guide with instructions, demonstration,
            calories burned and muscles worked. Learn proper form,
            discover all health benefits and choose
            a workout.
        </item>
        <item>High knees exercise guide with instructions,
            demonstration, calories burned and muscles worked. Learn proper form,
            discover all health benefits and choose a workout.
        </item>
        <item>Butt kicks exercise guide with instructions, demonstration,
            calories burned and muscles worked. Learn proper form,
            discover all health benefits and choose a workout.
        </item>
        <item>Knee and elbow press up exercise guide with instructions,
            demonstration, calories burned and muscles worked. Learn proper form,
            discover all health benefits and choose a workout.
        </item>
        <item>
            hamstring exercises to strengthen, tone , shape the back of your thighs!
            The hamstrings consist of three muscles located at the back of the upper thigh.
            These muscles are responsible for flexing the knees and assisting
            the glutes when we move the thigh backward and extend the hip.
        </item>
        <item> exercises to cinch the waist and sculpt your obliques!
            The obliques are the muscles located along the sides of the abdominal wall.
            These muscles are responsible for side bending and waist twisting moves.
            Working the obliques helps to sculpt and cinch the waist,
            tones the abdominal wall and tightens the midsection.
        </item>
        <item>Stutter steps exercise guide with instructions, demonstration,
            calories burned and muscles worked. Learn proper form,
            discover all health benefits and choose a workout.
        </item>
        <item>Top 16 exercises for getting rid of saddlebags!
            The outer thigh is a very common problem area for women.
            Hormones drive the deposition of fat around the pelvis, buttocks,
            and thighs and the fat deposits in the outer thighs, commonly know as saddlebags,
           </item>
        <item>Cross crunches exercise guide with instructions, demonstration,
            calories burned and muscles worked. Learn proper form,
            discover all health benefits and choose a workout.
        </item>
        <item>Back extensions exercise guide with instructions, demonstration,
            calories burned and muscles worked. Learn proper form,
            discover all health benefits and choose a workout.
        </item>
        <item>Shrimp squat exercise guide with instructions, demonstration,
            calories burned and muscles worked. Learn proper form,
            discover all health benefits and choose a workout.
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
